{
    "name" : "Maths 1",
    "format": "multiple_choice",
    "time": 15,
    "number_of_questions" : 10,
    "difficulty" : "Beginner",
    "type": "question_time",
    "questions" : [
        {
            "question" : "What is 4 + 6?",
            "answer_count": 2,
            "long_form": false,
            "answers" : [
                "10",
                "12"
            ],
            "correct_index" : 0
        },

        {
            "question" : "what is 6 รท 3?",
            "answer_count": 4,
            "long_form": false,
            "answers" : [
                "1",
                "3",
                "2",
                "6"
            ],
            "correct_index" : 2
        },

        {
            "question" : "what is 8 x 5?",
            "answer_count": 3,
            "long_form": false,
            "answers" : [
                "35",
                "45",
                "40"
            ],
            "correct_index" : 2
        },

        {
            "question" : "what is 6 - 10?",
            "answer_count": 4,
            "long_form": false,
            "answers" : [
                "-6",
                "-4",
                "0",
                "-3"
            ],
            "correct_index" : 1
        },
        {
            "question" : "what is 6 - 10?",
            "answer_count": 4,
            "long_form": false,
            "answers" : [
                "-6",
                "-4",
                "0",
                "-3"
            ],
            "correct_index" : 1
        },
        {
            "question" : "what is 6 - 10?",
            "answer_count": 4,
            "long_form": false,
            "answers" : [
                "-6",
                "-4",
                "0",
                "-3"
            ],
            "correct_index" : 1
        },
        {
            "question" : "what is 6 - 10?",
            "answer_count": 4,
            "long_form": false,
            "answers" : [
                "-6",
                "-4",
                "0",
                "-3"
            ],
            "correct_index" : 1
        },
        {
            "question" : "what is 6 - 10?",
            "answer_count": 4,
            "long_form": false,
            "answers" : [
                "-6",
                "-4",
                "0",
                "-3"
            ],
            "correct_index" : 1
        },
        {
            "question" : "what is 6 - 10?",
            "answer_count": 4,
            "long_form": false,
            "answers" : [
                "-6",
                "-4",
                "0",
                "-3"
            ],
            "correct_index" : 1
        },
        {
            "question" : "what is 6 - 10?",
            "answer_count": 4,
            "long_form": false,
            "answers" : [
                "-6",
                "-4",
                "0",
                "-3"
            ],
            "correct_index" : 1
        }
    ]
}